This girl's good.
這姑娘不錯啊
Oh yeah, a song with rhyming words.
哦，是的，一首押韻的歌。
I never thought of that before.
我以前從來沒想過這一點。
I like her.
我喜歡她。
Why, because she can sing and play guitar and do both at the
為什麼，因為她會唱歌和彈吉他，並且在學校裡兩者兼得
same time?
同一時間？
Well, that's pretty much all I'm looking for from these people.
嗯，這幾乎就是我從這些人身上尋找的一切。
Did you all jealous?
你們都嫉妒了嗎？
Come on, you two have completely different styles.
拜託，你們兩個的風格完全不同。
You know, she's more, you know, and you're more...
你知道，她更，你知道，你更…
See, everybody else is happy, she's done.
你看，其他人都很高興，她就完成了。
Okay, my next song's called Phoebe Buffay, What Can I Say?
好的，我的下一首歌叫做 Phoebe Buffay，我能說什麼？
I really loved when we were singing partners and I shouldn't have left
我真的很喜歡我們一起唱歌的時候，我不應該離開
you that way.
你那樣。
Oh no, one of those look for the hidden meaning songs.
喔不，其中一首尋找隱藏意義的歌曲。
Come on.
快點。
Hey, Leslie,
嘿，萊斯利，
how'd you know I'd be here?
你怎麼知道我會在這裡？
I ran into Vlad at the place where they sell the big fish
我在賣大魚的地方遇到了弗拉德
and he said you played here a lot, so...
他說你常在這裡玩，所以...
All right, listen, I have to go to the bathroom, but if the
好吧，聽著，我得去趟洗手間，但如果
place with the big fish comes up again, I'd like to know whether
有大魚的地方又出現了，我想知道是否
that's several big fish or just one big fish.
那是幾條大魚或只是一條大魚。
So, uh, Phoebe tells us you write jingles.
所以，呃，菲比告訴我們你寫歌。
Actually, I said she abandoned me to write jingles.
事實上，我說她拋棄我去寫歌曲了。
Anything we might have heard of?
我們可能聽過什麼嗎？
Uh, yeah, um...
呃，是的，嗯...
Home is never far away.
家從來不遠。
Home is Homestar Stew.
家是Homestar Stew。
Yeah, but I don't do that anymore.
是的，但我不再這樣做了。
I got kind of sick of it and then I couldn't come up
我有點厭倦瞭然後就上不來了
with anything good, so they fired me.
任何好的東西，所以他們解僱了我。
Bummer.
真糟糕。
Well, you know, I was just, um...
嗯，你知道，我只是，嗯...
I was just thinking and just hoping that maybe we'd want to get
我只是在想，只是希望也許我們想要得到
back together.
回到一起。
No, but thanks.
不，但是謝謝。
Oh, come on, Phoebe, would you just think about it?
哦，來吧，菲比，你能考慮一下嗎？
Okay.
好的。
No, but thanks.
不，但是謝謝。
Okay.
好的。
Okay, uh, see you, Pheebs.
好吧，呃，再見，菲比。
Wow, that was kind of brutal.
哇，這有點殘酷。
Well, okay, let this be a lesson to all of you, all right?
好吧，好吧，讓這成為你們所有人的教訓，好嗎？
Once you betray me, I become like the ice woman, you know?
一旦你背叛了我，我就會變得像冰女一樣，你知道嗎？
I'm just very cold, hard, unyielding.
我只是非常冷酷、堅硬、不屈服。
You know, nothing, nothing can penetrate this icy exterior.
你知道，沒有任何東西可以穿透這冰冷的外表。
Can I have a tissue, please?
請給我一張紙巾好嗎？
Someone in there?
裡面有人嗎？
No, this is just part of a daredevil game that I play called
不，這只是我玩的勇敢遊戲的一部分
wait until the last moment before I burst and die.
等到最後一刻我才爆發而死。
Jeez, man, did you fall high?
天哪，老兄，你摔得很高嗎？
So, uh, did you?
那麼，呃，你是嗎？
Did you fall high?
你摔得很高嗎？
Someone was in the ladies' room, I couldn't wait.
有人在女廁裡，我等不及了。
I left the lid up for you, though.
不過我把蓋子留給你了。
You know what, uh, go ahead, I'm talking to, uh...
你知道嗎，呃，繼續，我正在說話，呃......
This is the part where you'd say your name.
這是你要說出你的名字的部分。
Ginger.
姜。
Ginger, I'm talking to Ginger, so...
金傑，我正在和金傑說話，所以...
Don't you have to use the bathroom?
你不用上廁所嗎？
Nope, nope, I just, uh, I'd rather talk to you.
不，不，我只是，呃，我寧願和你談談。
Yes, I do.
是的，我願意。
Yes, I do have to go to the bathroom.
是的，我必須去趟洗手間。
Someone in here.
這裡有人。
Where's Chandler?
錢德勒在哪裡？
Uh, he can't make it, he said he had to go back to
呃，他來不了了，他說他必須回去
his, uh, job and do, uh...
他的，呃，工作和做的，呃…
Whoa-oh.
哇哦。
Joey?
喬伊？
Joey Tribbiani.
喬伊·崔比亞尼。
Joey, I can see you, okay?
喬伊，我看得到你，好嗎？
Joey, you're hiding behind the coats?
喬伊，你躲在外套後面嗎？
Close one.
關閉一個。
Hi.
你好。
Hi, sweetie.
嗨，親愛的。
Hello.
你好。
Hey, Russ.
嘿，拉斯。
Yeah?
是的？
I've got some bad news.
我有一些壞訊息。
What?
什麼？
I can get a quick bite to eat, but then I'm gonna have
我可以快速吃點東西，但之後我會
to come back up here.
回到這裡。
Come on, sweetie, you've had to work late every night for the past
來吧，親愛的，過去你每天都必須工作到很晚
two weeks.
兩週。
What is it this time?
這次是什麼？
Actually, it's kind of my fault.
事實上，這有點是我的錯。
I quit today.
我今天辭職了。
But work comes first.
但工作是第一位的。
Oh, hey, but that's sad about you, though.
哦，嘿，不過這對你來說是可悲的。
What happened?
發生了什麼事？
Burnout?
倦怠？
Burn all out, did ya?
燒盡一切，是嗎？
No, he's leaving for a better job.
不，他要離開去尋找更好的工作。
Oh, well, that's great.
哦，好吧，那太好了。
So I guess this is, uh, this is goodbye, then, huh?
所以我想這就是，呃，這是再見，嗯？
Goodbye.
再見。
Okay, then.
好吧，那麼。
Okay.
好的。
Well, we're gonna miss you around here.
好吧，我們會想念你的。
Yeah, me too.
是的，我也是。
So, see you on Saturday.
那麼，週六見。
Yeah, you bet.
是的，你打賭。
Ah!
啊!
Ugh.
啊。
You know those are a delicacy in India.
你知道那是印度的美味佳餚。
Yeah, that was Leslie calling again to see if we can get back
是的，萊斯利又打電話來看看我們是否可以回來
together.
一起。
It's like the 20th time today.
今天已經是第20次了。
Good luck, Leslie.
祝你好運，萊斯利。
Wow.
哇。
Must have hurt you pretty bad, huh?
一定傷得很重吧？
Well, yeah.
嗯，是的。
You know, we were best friends.
你知道，我們是最好的朋友。
Ever since we were little, our moms worked on the barge together.
從我們小的時候起，我們的媽媽就一起在駁船上工作。
Oh.
哦。
You two must have been so cute running around on a barge.
你們兩個在駁船上跑來跑去一定很可愛吧。
You never run on a barge.
你永遠不會在駁船上奔跑。
Hey.
嘿。
Is, uh, is Chandler around?
嗯，錢德勒在嗎？
No, um, he met some girl at the coffee house.
不，呃，他在咖啡館遇到了一個女孩。
Ooh.
哦。
Yeah.
是的。
Ginger something.
姜什麼的。
No.
不。
No, no.
不，不。
Uh, are you sure it wasn't something that sounded like ginger?
呃，你確定這不是聽起來像生薑的東西嗎？
Like, uh, uh, ginger?
就像，呃，呃，生薑？
No, it was ginger.
不，是生薑。
I remember because when he told me, I said, the movie star.
我記得是因為當他告訴我時，我說，電影明星。
Oh, man.
哦，夥計。
That's the girl I was hiding from.
這就是我一直躲著的女孩。
When she finds out he's my roommate, she's gonna tell him what I
當她發現他是我的室友時，她會告訴他我的事情
did.
做過。
Why, what did you do?
為什麼，你做了什麼？
Oh, oh, oh.
哦，哦，哦。
No, no, I can't.
不，不，我不能。
I can't tell you that.
我不能告訴你這一點。
It's like the most awful, horrible thing I've ever done in my whole
這就像我一生中做過的最可怕、最可怕的事情
life.
生活。
Well, you're really not making us want to hear it, Les.
好吧，萊斯，你真的不想讓我們聽。
But you know what?
但你知道嗎？
Don't tell us.
別告訴我們。
We'll just wait till Ginger gets home because it'll be more fun that
我們就等金傑回家吧，因為這樣會更有趣
way.
方式。
All right.
好的。
Okay, it was like four years ago.
好吧，就像四年前一樣。
Okay, Ginger and I had gone out a few times, and then this
好吧，我和金傑出去過幾次，然後這個
one weekend, we went up to her dad's cabin.
一個週末，我們去了她爸爸的小屋。
Just me, her, and her annoying little dog, Pepper.
只有我、她和她煩人的小狗佩柏。
Well, that night, I cooked this really romantic dinner.
好吧，那天晚上，我做了一頓非常浪漫的晚餐。
You gave her food poisoning.
你讓她食物中毒。
I wish.
我希望。
After dinner, me, her, and Pepper all fell asleep in front of the
晚餐後，我、她和Pepper都在床前睡著了。
fire.
火。
Well, I woke up in the middle of the night, and I saw
嗯，我半夜醒來，看到了
that the fire was dying out, so I picked up a log and
火快要熄滅了，所以我拿起一根木頭
threw it on.
把它扔在身上。
Or at least what I thought was a log.
或者至少我認為是一根木頭。
Oh, my God, you threw Pepper on the fire.
哦，天哪，你把 Pepper 扔到了火上。
I wish.
我希望。
See, I guess another thing I probably should have told you about Ginger
看，我想我應該告訴你關於薑的另一件事
is that she kind of has a, uh, artificial leg.
是她有一條，呃，假腿。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You threw it on the fire?
你把它丟到火上了嗎？
She must have freaked out.
她一定是嚇壞了。
Yeah, she must have.
是的，她一定有。
You don't know?
你不知道嗎？
Well, I...
嗯，我...
Joey, what did you do after you threw her leg on the fire?
喬伊，你把她的腿扔到火上之後做了什麼？
I ran.
我跑了。
You ran?
你跑了？
Yeah, through the woods with no socks on.
是的，不穿襪子穿過樹林。
Well, that's the best kiss I've had with anybody I met in a
嗯，這是我和任何人在一次約會中遇到的最好的一個吻
men's room.
男廁所。
Actually, me, too.
其實我也是。
Oh, foot in the puddle.
哦，腳踩到水坑裡了。
Foot all in the puddle.
腳全部踩在水坑裡。
Oh, damn.
哦，該死。
I hate that.
我討厭那樣。
Yeah, we're gonna have to get you out of those shoes.
是的，我們得把你脫掉。
Oh, don't worry about it.
哦，別擔心。
No, really, you're gonna freeze.
不，真的，你會凍僵的。
No, I'm not.
不，我不是。
You're not?
你不？
What are you...
你是什​​麼...
What are you, got a bionic foot?
你是什麼，有仿生腳嗎？
Someday, maybe.
也許有一天。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Any book?
有什麼書嗎？
Hmm?
唔？
Oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
I'm just thinking about something funny I heard today.
我只是在想今天聽到的一些有趣的事情。
Um, Mark...
嗯，馬克...
Mark's saying I'll see you Saturday.
馬克說週六見。
Yeah, at the lecture.
是的，在講座上。
I told you that last week.
我上週就告訴你了。
You said you didn't mind.
你說你不介意。
Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
It's...
這是...
It's not the lecture I mind.
我不介意這個講座。
Oh, please tell me it's not because I'm going with Mark.
哦，請告訴我這不是因為我要和馬克一起去。
Well...
嗯...
Oh, my God, Ross!
哦，天哪，羅斯！
Well, I'm sorry, but, uh...
好吧，我很抱歉，但是，呃...
Look, if you're not working with him anymore, why do you still have
聽著，如果你不再跟他一起工作了，為什麼你還要
to do stuff with him?
和他一起做事？
Because he's my friend.
因為他是我的朋友。
Okay, but do you really need another friend?
好吧，但你真的需要另一個朋友嗎？
Okay, well, if I stop playing with Joey and Chandler, can I play
好吧，如果我不再和喬伊和錢德勒一起玩，我可以玩嗎
with Mark?
和馬克？
Is that funny?
這很好笑嗎？
Am I supposed to be laughing?
我該笑嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道。
You thought see you Saturday was funny.
你以為週六見很有趣。
Look, honey, Mark is in fashion, okay?
親愛的，看，馬克很時尚，好嗎？
I like having a friend that I can share this stuff with.
我喜歡有一個可以跟我分享這些東西的朋友。
You guys would never want to go to a lecture with me.
你們永遠不會想跟我一起去聽講座。
Pah!
呸！
I would love to go with you.
我很願意和你一起去。
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Hey, I...
嘿，我...
I have clothes.
我有衣服。
I even pick them out.
我甚至把它們挑出來。
I mean, for...
我的意思是，為了...
for all you know, I could be a fashion...
就你所知，我可以成為時尚...
monger.
販子。
Okay.
好的。
Honey, I would love for you to go with me.
親愛的，我希望你能和我一起去。
What?
什麼？
What should I wear?
我該穿什麼？
Now I'm all nervous.
現在我很緊張。
You know, they say a watched pot never beeps.
你知道，他們說有人看管的鍋子永遠不會發出蜂鳴聲。
It's, you know, it's been a couple hours, and she hasn't called.
你知道，幾個小時過去了，她還沒打電話來。
Not that I even care.
我根本不在乎。
Don't.
不。
Why don't you just call her?
為什麼不直接打電話給她呢？
You obviously want to.
你顯然想要。
You think you know me so well.
你以為你很瞭解我。
Well, don't you wanna?
好吧，你不想嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Okay, so I do know you.
好吧，所以我確實認識你。
That's what I said.
我就是這麼說的。
Well, so?
嗯，所以呢？
I can't.
我不能。
She dumped me.
她甩了我。
I mean, I totally trusted her, and then one day, it was like,
我的意思是，我完全信任她，然後有一天，就像，
okay, bye, Pheebs, gone.
好吧，再見，菲比，走了。
You know what the saddest part is?
你知道最悲傷的部分是什麼嗎？
When we were playing together, that was, like, the most fun I've ever
當我們一起玩的時候，那是我玩過的最開心的事
had in, like, all my lives.
就像我一生一樣。
My favorite shoes, so good to me I wear them every day Down
我最喜歡的鞋子，對我來說太好了，我每天都穿它們
at the heel, holes in the toes Don't care what people say My
腳跟、腳趾上的洞別在意別人怎麼說我的
Pheebs best friend, pals to the end With them I'm one hot cheeky
菲比最好的朋友，永遠的好朋友，和他們在一起我就是一個厚臉皮的人
Though only one night, not much light I stepped in something icky Sticky
雖然只有一晚，光線不多，但我踩到了一些噁心的黏黏的東西
shoes, sticky shoes Always make me smile Sticky shoes, sticky shoes Next time
鞋子，黏鞋 總是讓我微笑 黏鞋，黏鞋 下次
I'll Avoid the Pile We're
我會避開我們現在的東西
beginning to see a lot of layering of sheer fabrics and colors.
開始看到很多透明布料和顏色的層次感。
I'm really glad we came.
我真的很高興我們來了。
You're so pretty.
你真漂亮。
I love you.
我愛你。
Smelly cat, smelly cat What are they feeding you?
臭貓臭貓他們給你吃什麼？
Smelly cat, smelly cat It's not your fault Wow, that's great.
臭貓臭貓這不是你的錯哇，太好了。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是嗎？
You know, you could totally sell this.
你知道，你完全可以賣掉這個。
It'd be perfect for, like, um, a kitty litter campaign.
這對於，嗯，貓砂運動來說是完美的。
A jingle?
順口溜？
No, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不。
Why not?
為什麼不呢？
You make a ton of money.
你賺了很多錢。
Okay, well, if I was in this for the money, I would be
好吧，如果我是為了錢，我就會
a millionaire by now, you know?
現在已經是百萬富翁了，你知道嗎？
You just gotta get out of that jingle head, sweetie.
你必須擺脫那個叮叮噹噹的頭腦，親愛的。
You're right.
你說得對。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
That's okay.
沒關係。
All right, I'm gonna play a song now that's really, really sad, okay?
好吧，我現在要演奏一首非常非常悲傷的歌，好嗎？
It's called Magician Box Mix-Up.
這就是所謂的魔術師盒子混合。
Okay.
好的。
Oversized bracelets, oversized earrings, oversized and accessories in general
超大手鐲、超大耳環、超大及一般配件
is very popular now.
現在很流行。
Garments with a Far Eastern influence are really breaking out this year.
受遠東影響的服裝今年確實爆發了。
Hi.
你好。
Hey.
嘿。
Okay for this?
可以嗎？
My milk's gone bad.
我的牛奶變質了
Oh, I hate that.
哦，我討厭那樣。
I once had a thing of half and half.
我曾經有過一半一半的事。
Stole my car.
偷了我的車。
So, um, how was your date with Ginger?
那麼，嗯，你和金傑的約會怎麼樣？
Great.
偉大的。
It was great.
太棒了。
She's, uh, she's great.
她，呃，她很棒。
Great looking, great personality.
顏值很高，個性也很好。
She's greatness.
她是偉大的。
Sounds like she's got the, uh, whole package.
聽起來她已經得到了，呃，整個包裹。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
So she's got it all, huh?
所以她已經得到了一切，對吧？
She's the real deal.
她是貨真價實的。
Joey told you about the leg, huh?
喬伊告訴你關於腿的事，是嗎？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Oh, God, it freaked me out, okay?
哦，天哪，這嚇到我了，好嗎？
I know it shouldn't have, but it did.
我知道不應該這樣，但它卻這樣做了。
I mean, I like her.
我是說，我喜歡她。
I don't want to stop seeing her, but every so often it's like,
我不想不再見她，但時常會這樣，
hey, you know what?
嘿，你知道嗎？
Where's your leg?
你的腿在哪裡？
I mean, I'm the smallest person in the world, aren't I?
我的意思是，我是世界上最小的人，不是嗎？
I'm the smallest person in the world.
我是世界上最小的人。
Morning.
早晨。
Actually, he's the smallest person in the world.
事實上，他是世界上最小的人。
Heard about the leg burning, huh?
聽說腿會燒傷，是嗎？
It came up.
它出現了。
Listen, I, uh, I know it's a long shot, but by any chance,
聽著，我，呃，我知道可能性不大，但無論如何，
did she find that funny?
她覺得這很有趣嗎？
So I nodded off a little.
於是我點點頭。
Nodded off?
點頭了？
Ross, you were snoring.
羅斯，你打鼾了。
My father's boat didn't make that much noise when it hit rocks.
我父親的船觸礁時並沒有發出那麼大的噪音。
Oh, come on, 45 minutes.
哦，來吧，45 分鐘。
45 minutes the man talked about strappy-back dresses.
45 分鐘，該男子談論了背帶連身裙。
Well, okay, how about four hours in a freezing museum auditorium listening to
好吧，在冰冷的博物館禮堂裡聽四小時怎麼樣？
Professor Pitstains in his, hey, everybody, remember that thing that's been
皮斯坦斯教授在他的，嘿，大家，記住那件事
dead for a gazillion years?
已經死了無數年了？
Well, here's that little bone we didn't know it had.
嗯，這是我們不知道它有的那根小骨頭。
First of all, it's Professor Pitstain.
首先是皮特斯坦教授。
And second of all, that little bone proved that that particular dinosaur had
其次，那根小骨頭證明瞭那個特定的恐龍
wings but didn't fly.
翅膀卻沒有飛翔。
Okay, so you know what I just heard?
好吧，你知道我剛剛聽到了什麼嗎？
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉，巴拉。
You don't know it.
你不知道。
A hundred million people went to see a movie about what I do.
一億人去看了一部關於我所做的事情的電影。
I wonder how many people would go see a movie called Jurassic Park.
我想知道有多少人會去看一部叫《侏羅紀公園》的電影。
Jurassic Park-a.
侏羅紀公園-a.
Oh, that was so...
哦，原來如此…
I don't know, a bunch of out-of-control jackets take over an
我不知道，一群失控的夾克接管了
island.
島。
You know, if what I do is so lame, then why did you
你知道，如果我做的事情如此蹩腳，那你為什麼還要這麼做？
insist on coming with me this morning?
今天早上堅持要跟我一起去嗎？
Huh, was it so I just wouldn't go with Mark?
呃，是不是我就不會跟馬克一起去？
No.
不。
I...
我...
I wanted to be with you.
我想和你在一起。
I don't know, I feel like lately, I feel like you're slipping away
我不知道，我感覺最近，我感覺你正在溜走
from me, you know, with this new job and all these new people
來自我，你知道，有了這份新工作和所有這些新人
and got this whole of the life going on.
並讓這整個生活繼續下去。
I know it's dumb, but I just hate that I'm not a part
我知道這很愚蠢，但我只是討厭我不參與其中
of it.
它的。
It's not dumb.
這並不愚蠢。
But maybe it's okay that you're not a part of it.
但也許你不參與其中也沒關係。
You know what I mean?
你知道我的意思？
I mean, it's like, I like that you're not involved in that part
我的意思是，我喜歡你不參與那部分
of my life.
我的生活。
That's a little clearer.
這樣就清楚一點了。
Honey, see, it doesn't mean that I don't love you, because I do,
親愛的，你看，這並不代表我不愛你，因為我愛你，
I love you, I love you so much.
我愛你，我很愛你。
But my work, it's for me, you know, I'm out there on my
但我的工作是為了我自己，你知道，我在外面
own, and I'm doing it, and it's scary, but I love it because
自己，我正在這樣做，這很可怕，但我喜歡它，因為
it's mine.
這是我的。
But, I mean, is that okay?
但是，我的意思是，這樣可以嗎？
Sure, rather.
當然，相反。
You're thinking about my leg, aren't you?
你在想我的腿，不是嗎？
What?
什麼？
No, actually, I forgot.
不，實際上，我忘記了。
What is the deal with that again?
這又有什麼關係呢？
It's okay if it bothers you.
如果打擾你也沒關係。
Really, I mean, the only thing I need to know is how much
真的，我的意思是，我唯一需要知道的是多少
it bothers you, because I don't like wasting my time.
這讓你很煩惱，因為我不喜歡浪費時間。
Am I wasting my time?
我是在浪費時間嗎？
No, no, I don't think so.
不，不，我不這麼認為。
Honey, it's just like anything else, you just have to get used to
親愛的，就像其他事情一樣，你只需要習慣
it.
它。
What's that?
那是什麼？
That's, that's my nubbin.
那就是，那是我的小妞。
What's a nubbin?
什麼是尼賓？
It's kind of a, uh, a third nipple kind of thing.
這是一種，呃，第三個乳頭之類的東西。
So you have three nipples?
那你有三個乳頭嗎？
Well, you know, two regulars.
嗯，你知道，兩個常客。
And, uh, one that barely qualifies as a...
而且，呃，一個勉強夠資格成為...
Uh, what?
呃，什麼？
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
I just remembered I have to leave.
我才想起我必須離開。
You, uh, you have to leave now?
你，呃，你現在必須離開嗎？
How come?
怎麼會？
Oh, well, it's nubbin.
哦，好吧，這是個小東西。
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
No, I'm, I'm, I'm...
不，我是，我是，我是…
I'll see you later.
稍後見。
Okay.
好的。
Uh...
呃...
Oh, I thought you weren't coming.
哦，我以為你不來了。
Where, where were you?
哪裡，你在哪裡？
Come here, come here.
過來，過來。
Okay.
好的。
Don't get mad, okay?
別生氣，好嗎？
Okay, don't give me a reason to get mad, okay?
好吧，別給我生氣的理由，好嗎？
I played smelly cat for the people of my old ad agency.
我為我以前的廣告公司的人扮演臭貓。
They went nuts.
他們瘋了。
No, look, I told you that I didn't want you to try and
不，聽著，我告訴過你我不想讓你嘗試
sell it, and you just, you big fat did it anyway.
賣掉它，你就，你這個大胖子還是這麼做了。
Good.
好的。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
I think five years ago, I probably would have done anything to play
我想五年前，我可能會做任何事來玩
with you, but I can do it by myself, right?
和你一起，但我自己可以做到，對嗎？
And if I can't trust you, then just forget it.
如果我不能信任你，那就忘了吧。
No, no, I don't want to forget it.
不，不，我不想忘記它。
Okay, you know what?
好吧，你知道嗎？
You have to choose, all right?
你必須選擇，好嗎？
If, if the most important thing on the planet to you is this
如果，如果這個星球上對你來說最重要的事情就是這個
cat poopy thing, then...
貓便便的東西，然後...
Okay, you can have smelly cat, but we won't be partners.
好吧，你可以養臭貓，但我們不會成為夥伴。
So what's it gonna be?
那麼會是什麼呢？
Problem order in the litter box?
垃圾箱的順序有問題嗎？
Don't change your kitty, change your kitty litter.
不要改變你的小貓，而是改變你的貓砂。
Sorry, Pheebs.
對不起，菲比斯。
Yeah, you okay?
是啊，你還好嗎？
Yeah, I actually am, yeah.
是的，我確實是，是的。
Because, you know, life's, life's gonna hand you all kinds of stuff.
因為，你知道，生活會給你各種各樣的東西。
You know, you learn your little lessons, and hopefully you grow.
你知道，你學到了一些小教訓，希望你能成長。
Want to hear a new song?
想聽一首新歌嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
I'd love to.
我喜歡。
Okay.
好的。
Jingle bitch screwed me over Go to hell, jingle whore Go to hell,
叮噹母狗把我搞砸了去死吧，叮噹母狗去地獄吧，
go to hell Go to hell, go to hell That's all I have
去地獄吧 去地獄吧 去地獄吧 這就是我的全部
so far.
迄今為止。
Woo-hoo!
嗚呼！
Where have you been?
你去哪裡了？
The doctor.
醫生。
Is everything okay?
一切都好嗎？
Oh, yes.
哦是的。
Just had me a little nubinectomy.
剛剛為我做了一點努賓切除手術。
Yep.
是的。
Two nipples, no waiting.
兩個乳頭，無需等待。
Wow.
哇。
Just like Rachel in high school.
就像高中時的雷切爾一樣。
What?
什麼？
Oh, my.
哦，我的。
Come on.
快點。
I was kidding.
我開玩笑的。
It was such an obvious joke.
這真是個明顯的笑話。
That was an obvious joke.
這是一個明顯的玩笑。
And I didn't think of it.
而我卻沒有想到。
Why didn't I think of it?
我怎麼沒想到呢？
The source of all my powers.
我所有力量的泉源。
Oh, dear God, what have I done?
噢，親愛的上帝，我做了什麼？